# Daniel Fasula

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

Cell: 208-447-0035 danielfasula@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/danielfasula/ GitHub: github.com/danielfasula

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

#### SUMMARY

Software Developer with 500+ hours of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery and maintenance. A fast learner with strong time management and multi-tasking skills. Strong work ethic in team or individual settings to drive product success and process efficiency.

- Javascript - Communication - Critical Thinking - Firebase - HTML - Creativity - Vue3 - Patience - Confidence - Node.is - Visual Studios - Accountability - SCRUM /AGILE - Teamwork - MVC - Auth0 - SASS - Wireframing - C# - Bootstrap - MongoDB - Restful API's

- GitHub

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Software Developer Student**

CODE WORKS FEB 2021 - APR 2021

- -Developed over 30 web-based applications within 13 weeks with over 500+ hours of programming experience
- -Experienced working in a team setting or as an individual to produce MVPs within proper time boxes
- -Acquired the knowledge and tools to be able to apply SCRUM to a workload in order to produce quality work in appropriate amounts of time
- -Producing efficient and elegant code based on requirements
- -Testing and deploying programs and applications
- -Troubleshooting, debugging, maintaining and improving existing software

### **Certified Pharmacy Technician**

ST. LUKE'S OUTPATIENT PHARMACY | JUL 2020 - JAN 2021 CVS PHARMACY | OCT 2019 - JUL 2020 FRED MEYER | AUG 2018 - OCT 2019 ALBERTSONS | APR 2015 - AUG 2018

- -Communicating with other health care providers, reviewing patient records, provide immunizations and filling medication orders while following HIPPA guidelines
- -In charge of overseeing multiple projects simultaneously
- -Provide courteous customer service and assist the Pharmacist on duty in maintaining the clean and orderly appearance of the pharmacy area, prioritizing work, and processing prescription orders in compliance with Federal and State laws and company policies and procedures.
- -Sorting, stocking and labeling medications and monitoring inventory

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Code Works**

FEB 2021 - APR 2021